# KHLOE BROWN

FRONT-END DEVELOPER & GRAPHIC DESIGNER

(513) 633-4326 hello@khloeabrown.com www.khloeabrown.com

#### **PROFILE**

Front-End Developer & Graphic Designer with 6+ years of experience creating beautiful, effective and (of course) functional websites and marketing media for growing businesses and aspiring entrepreneurs. Categorized into two specialties: front-end web developer learning the MERN stack with an eye for UI and a graphic designer creating beautiful logos, brand identities, and marketing media.

#### **OBJECTIVE**

To be hired for a web designer position with a friendly, professional and work-dedicated employer in the technology or design industry. Preferably, said position would include hands-on opportunities with code and design on projects and with clients.

## **ABILITIES**

## **Development**

Proficient - HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Sass Familiar - git, npm, SQL, React.js, Bootstrap, Parcel

#### Design

UX & analysis, UI & layout design, mockups, prototyping, Adobe Creative Suite

# **AWARDS**

Dean's List @ Cincinnati State

2018, Student

Programmer of the Year @ Butler Tech

Jun 2016, Student

1st Place @ SkillsUSA

Mar 2016, Web Design Team

3rd Place @ Business Professionals of America

Feb 2016, Web Design Team

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Graphic Designer @ Trinity Church Supply**

Oct 2018 - Aug 2020

- Designed cards and printed materials for new products to increase sales and company branding.
- Worked collaboratively with supervisors, other associates, and freelancing designers to create new projects.
- Organized, documented and outlined a product catalog to dole out to churches and organizations.
- Trained new employees for documenting incoming products.

# Tutor and Desk Assistant @ Cincinnati State

Oct 2016 - Dec 2018

- Assisted and mentored web development and graphic design students by explaining code samples, reteaching web dev lessons, and providing personal examples of work.
- Maintained order and direction within the tutoring room as an assistant.

## **EDUCATION**

#### Cincinnati State Technical and Community College

Associate in Web and Multimedia Design, 2016 - 2021

- Excelled in my studies with web design.
- Assisted friends and classmates with class projects and studies.
- Received Dean's List Award in 2018.
- Classes Include: Web Dev 1 & 2, JavaScript, 2D Graphics, Advanced Web Topics and Marketing.